



Profile

De event world is constantly changing. Like my personal life:

From making live music with a band towards the present: finding the love of my life, getting married and emigrating to Spain.

My work experience: Growing in 7 years in 1 company, this gives myself and the director of the company, confidence to keep growing and be the best.

The WOW -effect is what I want to create every day for clients. Before, during and after the event. This gives me energy.

I am a team player and I am sharing my energy. "A good and trusted client is a returning client."

Education

2007 - 2011

Leisure Management Higher Vocational Education

2010 - 2011 Minor Event Management

Higher Vocational Education (University "Stenden hogeschool" in Leeuwarden at the Netherlands.)

(University "Stenden hogeschool" in Leeuwarden, the Netherlands.)

Tourism recreational education

(School "Noorderpoort College"

in Groningen, the Netherlands)

Experiences

Event manager & Account manager | *Jaarbeurs*

Start September 2022 - April 2023

Business meeting center, MeetUp - Remote (Madrid) #My role @MeetUp - Remote

Daily contact with our clients by email and phone

Advice in technique (hybrid) possibilities

Advice in Food & Beverage

Meetings from 1 person until 170 persons a meeting

Organized 370 meetings in 34 weeks

Conference & Business Events - Onsite

#Extra: https://youtu.be/DAGSYUAJA-k- working/appearing in marketing videos.

1998-2003

2003-2007

High school

College Mavo

(School "Bogerman College" in Sneek, the Netherlands).

Event manager & Account manager | Jaarbeurs

Start September 2019

Languages

Spanish: A1-> Speaking Spanish: A2-> Reading

English: C1 Dutch: Native Frisian: Native German: B2 French: A1 Daily contact with our clients by email and phone

Regular returning customers, personal contact with

My role @Conferences & Business Events - On site (Utrecht)

Find the most suited room for every meeting

Advice in technique (hybrid) possibilities

Meetings from 6 person until 600 persons a meeting

Events for 1 day or 2 days

23 events plus 100 persons

Example events

Knowledge

Technologies

Software

Cvent/ Amex Pardot

WebEx / Zoom / Teams

Excel - Word - Power Point Ungerboeck / Momentus

lecture – Dinner – Care conferences for professionals – employee meetings 'Mc Donald's' – New Year's meetings – Training – seminar – symposia – studio event

#Extra: https:/youtu.be/cdDVZ0F0shk%20/ Video Conferences & Business Events Jaarbeurs



Experiences

Service employee | *Jaarbeurs* #My role Sales support team - *On site*

22 fairs a year

Client support before, during and after the fair

+/- 850 questions and solutions a day during the fair

Providing optimal service for each client

Creating onboarding project new colleagues in Sales support team

Team leader (group of 10) and point of contact for colleagues

......

Junior account manager | *Jaarbeurs* #My role account manager junior - *On site*

Start June 2016

Start June 2017

Generate leads by phone and email

Extend the database through Sales Flow

Sales manager | *De Landgoederij & Kasteel Cammingha* #My role sales manager - *On site*

Start March 2016

Responsible for the private market of sales of both locations. Leading the entire sales process with the right quotes and handling of this.

Mainly to private individuals (wedding couples)

Arranging guided tours, quotation discussions and detailed agreements, both by telephone and on location

Confirming the agreements made and drawing up quotations

Drafting and transferring work letters

Ordering and arranging of, among other things, technology, furnishing and styling for the locations for the benefit of each event

Supporting (all kinds of) sales and commercial activities of the entire sales team

Jointly responsible for achieving the turnover targets

After sales and relationship management

Sales manager | Inn Style #My role sales manager - On site Start March 2015

Responsible for the entire sales process

Evaluation and handling of an event.

Conducting commercial customer interviews and conducting site visits and accepting quotes

Coming up with programs and concepts

Writing good impressions of the atmosphere

Drawing up quotations and confirmations

Arrange options and reservations for suppliers

Making scenarios for the event and ensuring a clear transfer

Process financial settlement of events and after sales